Georgette Bondarek

Contact Information



252,536,1080



GeorgetteBondarek@Gmail.com



Carolina Beach, NC

EDUCATION

Coding Bootcamp

UNC Chapel Hill Currently Enrolled

Business Administration/Marketing Minor Biology

North Carolina Wesleyan College 2002 - 2007

Summary

Progressive leadership with extensive experience in managing, teaching, and educating others. Strives to effectively build loyalty and long-lasting relationships with team members and clients. Specifically excels at understanding consumer and business needs while keeping up-to-date with data trends and technological solutions to meet organizational goals.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

U.S. Cellular / Wilmington, NC / December 2010 - August 2020

BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT MANAGER

- Analyzes market data to develop plan to increase knowledge and sales to business customers within market
- Trained 150 associates and leaders within eastern North Carolina market around understanding the value of business customers and how to effectively close sales
- Increased territory business sales by 35% in 8 months
- Identify content and application partnership opportunities relative to customer interest/demand with Internet of Technology solutions
- Build and present proposals to present to other business organizations and negotiate partnership agreements
- Manage, coach, and guide team members to help maximize the client experience
- Conducted onsite implementation of complex solutions with clients
- Met and exceeded personal prospecting goal each month, and met during COVID-19 while transitioned to working remotely

BUSINESS SALES SUPPORT SPECIALIST

- Created additional supporting documents to help account executive illustrate complex solutions for clients that included data analysis for compared return on their investment and education
- Lead initiative in peer group to 'house' a shared document virtually for centralized sales tracking and organized clients' current solutions
- Chosen to work on Account Review project to enhance customer experience and retention
- Completed company research for clients, and assisted with implementation of Internet of Things solutions
- Expert on Internet of Solutions with defined partnerships, and facilitated solution implementations

RETAIL WIRELESS SALES CONSULTANT

- Assisted leadership with on boarding new hires, training, and delivering additional peer to peer support
- Conducted and lead educational seminars with customers on the newest technology as well as provided instruction on their current solutions
- Exceeded Customer experience according to U.S. Cellular Scale

Altheramune / Rocky Mount, NC / March 2010 - February 2012

PHARMACEUTICAL SALES RESPRESENTATIVE - Immunotherapy

- Solicited new business across Eastern North Carolina for Immunotherapy
- Fostered professional relationships with physicians and office staff to uncover potential and needs of the location
- Educated and trained physicians and staff on product knowledge, and insurance billing of immunotherapy through visits and luncheons
- Scheduled "Blood Draw" days within office, after physician identified target patients
- Analyzed territory data to plan weekly, monthly site visits, while prioritizing areas that yielding higher market share to own business
- Met company certifications and maintained company budget guidelines

KEY SKILLS

Organization and Prioritization

Analytical Thinking/Planning

Strong Interpersonal Communication Skills

Accuracy and Attention to Details

Problem Solving

Team Leadership

Decision Making

ALLSTATE / Roanoke Rapids, NC / February 2009 – May 2010

OFFICE MANAGER

- Implemented marketing strategy, through local radio, restaurant ads, and little league sports
- Set and executed standards for customer service within office
- Researched and handled complaints made by customers, to make sure the customer had the best experience

Sepracor / Rocky Mount, NC / July 2008 -March 2009

CONTRACT PHARMACEUTICAL SALES RESPRESENTATIVE

- Highly Functional contract representative through Publicis Selling Solution for the Sepracor Pharmaceuticals Corporation, for launch of new drug Alvesco and existing respiratory products for central and eastern North Carolina cities including but not limited to Wilson, Rocky Mount, Louisburg, Elizabeth City, and Nags Head
- Successfully launched Alvesco, an ICS drug, increased sales performance for Omnaris, an INS drug, and grew sales of Xopenex a type of Levalbuterol
- Applied an in-depth understanding of the industry to consistently acquire new, generate referrals, and retain existing professional client relationship with Pediatricians, Pulmonologists, Allergists, and healthcare professionals at Family Medical Practices, in Eastern North Carolina.
- Fostered professional relationships with physicians and office staff to uncover potential and needs of the location